michaelpage.co.in 2012-11-06

# Privacy Policy - Michael Page International

Michael Page International Ltd and our related companies worldwide ("Michael Page International") are committed to protecting the privacy of our candidates, clients and other users of our websites and services.

Where you provide us with your personal data, in person, by email, through this website or through any of our other international websites or offices, we will endeavour to ensure that such information remains private and is only used in accordance with this policy. By providing us with your personal data, you also consent for us to collect, hold, use and disclose your personal data in accordance with this policy. Michael Page International must comply with the applicable privacy laws and similar laws in the countries in which we operate.

**1\. Collection of Personal Data  
** Michael Page International may collect your personal information from you, including (without limitation) your name, contact details, qualifications, work history, your right to work in a particular country, languages spoken, professional memberships and accreditations, your work objectives and other information from your CV. If you are to be considered for a particular position, we may also collect references from your nominated referees. All the personal data we collect is held, used and disclosed for the purposes set out below.

**2\. Use and Disclosure of Personal Data** Michael Page International holds, uses and discloses your personal data for the following purposes:

(a) to provide our services to you;

(b) to maintain our business relationship, where you are a user of our  website, a client or candidate;

(c) to enable you to submit your CV generally, to apply for specific jobs or to subscribe to our Job Alerts;

(d) to match your coded details with job vacancies, to assist us in finding a position that is most suitable for you and, where you provide your prior consent as a candidate, to send your personal data to clients in order to apply for jobs;

(e) to answer your inquiry;

(f) to direct-market products and services, advise you of news and industry updates, events, promotions and competitions, reports and other information. Where we do so, you will be able to unsubscribe from such communications;

(g) where you are registered as a candidate on our database, your personal data will be accessible by our other offices internationally, in the UK, Europe, Asia Pacific and the Americas;

(h) to different parts of the Michael Page International Group worldwide to enable the development and marketing of other products and services and to improve our customer service and to make our services more valuable to you, including tailoring our website when you log on to make it relevant to you personally;

(i) to trusted third parties where we have retained them to provide services that you have requested, such as psychometric evaluations or skills tests, and who also provide services to us, such as professional advisers, IT consultants, mailing houses and function co-ordinators. These third parties must comply with similar undertakings of privacy and confidentiality as Michael Page International;

(j) if Michael Page International merges with or is acquired by another business, we may share personal data with the new owners of the business and their advisers and if this happens, you will be sent notice of such an event;

(k) we may also release personal data to regulatory or law enforcement authorities, if they require us to do so; and

(l) we may also seek your consent to collect, hold, use and disclose your personal data for any other purpose not listed above.

**3\. Privacy on Our Websites  
** (a) Submitting Your Curriculum Vitae ("CV") and Applying for Jobs

You may submit your CV to Michael Page International via this website, either for general consideration by our recruitment consultants for positions as they arise or to apply for a specific advertised job. Once submitted, your CV will be sent directly to the relevant Michael Page International recruitment consultant who will review your details and advise you whether you are to be accepted by us for registration on our central database. This database, including your personal data, can be accessed by any of our recruitment consultants working in other offices of the Michael Page International Group, both inside and outside India. If you are accepted onto our database, our recruitment consultants should then contact you to set up an interview in person. You can update your CV at any time, simply by following the same procedure to submit a new CV via our websites.

(b) Job Alerts

You may sign up to receive emails that alert you to new jobs on our website (Job Alerts). To subscribe to Job Alerts, you need to provide your email address, which will be used for the purpose of keeping you informed by email of the latest jobs and/or news in your nominated industry. If you no longer wish to receive Job Alerts, unsubscribe links are provided in every Job Alert email that you receive.

(c) Aggregate Information About Website Visitors

We gather information and statistics about all visitors to this and all of our websites worldwide, including the most frequently accessed pages and most frequently used services. We only use such data in aggregate form (that is, the information does not identify any one individual). This information helps us determine the most beneficial parts of our websites and ways in which we can continually improve our online services to create a better overall experience for our users. We also publish some of this aggregate (non-identifiable) information on the Michael Page International websites worldwide.

(d) Cookies

A cookie is a small data file which is sent from our web server to your individual web browser when your browser visits our server's website. You can find out more about the use of cookies on [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/). Cookies are used on Michael Page International websites to remember your login details, to track web traffic on an aggregate basis and to keep session information in cache to assist your use of our website, such as your last search (however, this information is disposed of every time you close your web browser). Most browsers allow you to turn off cookies (see the help menu on your browser), however, switching off cookies will restrict your use of our websites.

**4\. Access to Personal Data  
** You may request access to or updating of your personal data held at Michael Page International by contacting the Michael Page International privacy officer as set out below. We may ask to verify your identity and for more information about your request. Where we are legally permitted to do so, we may refuse your request and give you reasons for doing so. Where you request your personal data to be updated and there is a dispute about the facts, we will make a note on your personal data of such dispute. You may also request that Michael Page International stops using your information and contacting you and we will comply with your request. However, if this involves a request for deletion of your file, please be aware that we may not be required or able to do so, particularly where your file also holds information about our clients. Where permitted to do so, we may charge an administrative fee for access and updating requests.

**5\. Security  
** Michael Page International takes reasonable steps to keep personal data secure, accurate and up to date. The Internet is not always a secure method of transmitting information. Accordingly, while we seek to protect your personal data by implementing digital security systems in various parts of our website, Michael Page International cannot accept responsibility for the security of information you send to or receive from us over the Internet or for any unauthorised access or use of that information. Where we have links to websites outside the Michael Page International Group, we cannot ensure that your privacy will be protected in accordance with this policy. You should consult these other websites' privacy policies as we have no control over them and are not responsible for any information that is submitted to or collected by these third parties.

**6\. Changes to this Privacy Policy  
** Michael Page International may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. We suggest that you visit our website regularly to keep up to date with any changes. 

**7\. Contact  
** You can contact our Privacy Officer as follows:

[privacyofficer@michaelpage.co.in](mailto:privacyofficer@michaelpage.co.in):                       
+91 (0) 22 4368 8000  
Michael Page International Recruitment Private Limited  
Level 12 Express Towers  
Nariman Point, Mumbai, India
